export const quizData = [
    {
        question: "Where is the Acropolis of Rhodes located?",
        options: ["Lindos", "Kamiros", "Rhodes City", "Tsambika"],
        correctOption: "Rhodes City"
    },
    {
        question: "Which ancient site was home to the Temple of Athena Lindia?", 
        options: ["Ancient Ialyssos", "Lindos Acropolis", "Acropolis of Rhodes", "Kamiros"],
        correctOption: "Lindos Acropolis"
    },
    {
        question: "What natural attraction is named for its butterflies?",
        options: ["The Seven Springs", "Butterfly Valley", "Lindos Beach", "Tsambika Beach"],
        correctOption: "Butterfly Valley"
    },
    {
        question: "Which attraction in Rhodes was known as one of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World?",
        options: ["Lindos Acropolis", "Temple of Apollo", "Palace of the Grand Master", "Colossus of Rhodes"],
        correctOption: "Colossus of Rhodes"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of natural feature is Tsambika Beach known for?",
        options: ["Rocky shore", "Golden sand", "Forested cliffs", "Volcanic rock"],
        correctOption: "Golden sand"
    },
    {
        question: "In which location can you find the Temple of Athena Polias?",
        options: ["Tsambika", "Ancient Kamiros", "Ancient Ialyssos", "The Seven Springs"],
        correctOption: "Ancient Ialyssos"
    },
    {
        question: "What is one of the highlights of visiting Lindos Beach?",
        options: ["The Temple of Apollo", "Views of the acropolis", "Guided boat tours", "Wildlife sanctuary"],
        correctOption: "Views of the acropolis"
    },
    {
        question: "Where can you find a blend of medieval and Gothic architecture in Rhodes?",
        options: ["Lindos Acropolis", "Palace of the Grand Master", "The Seven Springs", "Kamiros"],
        correctOption: "Palace of the Grand Master"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a unique feature of the Seven Springs?",
        options: ["A river running underground", "Seven natural springs flowing through the forest", "Ancient ruins", "Sandy beach"],
        correctOption: "Seven natural springs flowing through the forest"
    },
    {
        question: "The Temple of Apollo is located at which site?",
        options: ["The Seven Springs", "Ancient Ialyssos", "Rhodes City", "Kamiros"],
        correctOption: "Rhodes City"
    },
    {
        question: "Which beach is known for its picturesque setting and watersports activities?",
        options: ["Lindos Beach", "Butterfly Valley", "Tsambika Beach", "The Seven Springs"],
        correctOption: "Tsambika Beach"
    },
    {
        question: "Where can you find the ancient stadium used for athletic competitions in Rhodes?",
        options: ["Lindos Acropolis", "Acropolis of Rhodes", "Kamiros", "Palace of the Grand Master"],
        correctOption: "Acropolis of Rhodes"
    },
    {
        question: "In which town is the Palace of the Grand Master located?",
        options: ["Kamiros", "Rhodes City", "Lindos", "Ialyssos"],
        correctOption: "Rhodes City"
    },
    {
        question: "What is one of the features of Lindos Acropolis?",
        options: ["The Temple of Athena Lindia", "The Knights' palace", "Casino facilities", "Underground springs"],
        correctOption: "The Temple of Athena Lindia"
    },
    {
        question: "What is unique about the Colossus of Rhodes?",
        options: ["It's still standing today", "It was the tallest statue of the ancient world", "It's located in Kamiros", "It was built by knights"],
        correctOption: "It was the tallest statue of the ancient world"
    },
    {
        question: "What is an attraction you can visit near Ancient Ialyssos?",
        options: ["The Acropolis of Rhodes", "Lindos Beach", "A nearby beach", "Butterfly Valley"],
        correctOption: "A nearby beach"
    },
    {
        question: "In which location can you find an underground passage to a lake?",
        options: ["The Seven Springs", "Tsambika Beach", "Ancient Ialyssos", "Casino Rodos"],
        correctOption: "The Seven Springs"
    },
    {
        question: "Which destination is known for its golden sand and panoramic views?",
        options: ["Tsambika Beach", "Palace of the Grand Master", "Butterfly Valley", "Ancient Kamiros"],
        correctOption: "Tsambika Beach"
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the Temple of Apollo located in Rhodes?",
        options: ["Butterfly Valley", "Kamiros", "Acropolis of Rhodes", "Ancient Ialyssos"],
        correctOption: "Acropolis of Rhodes"
    },
    {
        question: "What is one of the main reasons tourists visit the Palace of the Grand Master?",
        options: ["Beach access", "Ancient Greek ruins", "Medieval architecture and artifacts", "Hiking trails"],
        correctOption: "Medieval architecture and artifacts"
    },
    {
        question: "The Acropolis of Rhodes is located in which area of the island?",
        options: ["Ialyssos", "Rhodes City", "Kamiros", "Lindos"],
        correctOption: "Rhodes City"
    }
]